Creativediversity7@gmail.com
213-215-7439
Los Angeles, Ca 90044
DON CARLOUS DAVIS

## Professional Summary:

Twelve years of experience providing comprehensive and resourceful technical support. Information Technology Support Technician experience accessing, installing, configuring, administering, and supporting a broad range of computer system and network system solutions. Ensuring optimal functionality, reliability and stability. Dependable resource for significant clients such as: Ernst & Young, Disney, Warner Bros, Morgan Stanley, Liberty Mutual, Albertsons, American Airlines, LAWAA, Alcoa, 7-11, Chase Bank, and Best Buy to only name a few.

- Committed to helping organizations achieve maximum benefit from their IT infrastructure investment through meticulous upgrades/installs/migrations solid system support, complete user training and on time project deliveries.
- Proficient at mastering new or proprietary technologies and effectively applying them in the workplace. Easily adapt to diverse corporate infrastructures.
- Consistently recognized for exemplary quality and service for achieving above expected expectations. Efforts have been instrumental in elevating client's reputation and relationships enterprise-wide.
- Tenacious troubleshooter that brings energy, enthusiasm and leadership to problem difficult problems. Dedicated to giving tireless effort towards problem resolution.

_					
1 4	ach	mica	יו כי	νıI	ıc.
		11 III <i>.c</i>	11	nн	1.5

Hardware: Troubleshooting and repairing of network hardware, workstations, laptops, printers, retail systems (time clocks, registers, scales, and scanners), and technology peripherals. Hands-on experience in all the leading brands, including Apple, Lenovo, IBM, NCR, Packard Bell, Sony, Dell, Toshiba, NEC, HP, Epson, Lexmark, and Okidata network printers.

Networking: LAN/WAN connectivity, TCP/IP, Ethernet, Network components (routers, switches, hubs, cabling).

Applications: Servicenow, HP Service Manager, Microsoft Office 365(Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook), Quicken, Lotus Notes

Platforms: Windows 10/ 7/Vista/XP/2000/ Mac OS\.

Professional Experience

Premier Logic (Ernst & Young)

Dec. 2nd to Present

IT Support Specialist

Managed data migration schedules for 2200 user base Provided Imaging, Deployment, Configuration, Desktop Support, and migration of users' workstations using USMT and SCCM from Windows 7 operating system to the Windows 10 platform, ensuring all data, applications, files and folders migrations are completed efficiently and with minimum interruption of operations. Provided Post Support for end-users for my team as needed to ensure optimal deployment of resources.

Abbtech(Warner Bros)

May 31 2019 to Dec 2019

Desktop Technician

Provided support for Deployment, configuration and migration of 1500 users' workstations from Windows 7 operating system to the Windows 10 platform, ensuring all data, applications, files and folders migrations are completed efficiently and with minimum interruption of operations.

Provided Post Support for end-users for my team as needed t resources.	to ensure optimal deployment of			
Disney				
Desktop Technician	March 2012 to Sept 20 2018			
Responsible for the deployment and desktop support for the 6	6600 Disney Cast members.			
Responsible for the complete migration of the Executive lapto Windows moving all data including all applications and fixing a large scale Cast Member moves, leading up to 12 technicians	all problems. Serve as lead on all			
Representative achievement:				
Compucom (Albertsons Grocery Stores)				
POS Technician	April 2011 to March 2012			
Removed old NCR POS registers/ printers /scanners / scales and installed new ones in front lanes and specialty areas for improved performance. Programmed and thoroughly tested all new equipment.				
Representative achievement: Letter of recognition written from Support Team for	n the Albertsons CPOS In-Store			
great attitude and on time store openings.				
Smartsource				

Worked on numerous consulting assignments in the Los Angeles metro area performing hardware and

August 2010 to 2012

Computer Technician

software installs, POS installations and printer configurations for various clients/customers of Smartsource.

Representative achievement: Ensured numerous software upgrades and hardware installs were completed smoothly with no issues.

The Norland Group

Computer Technician

February 2010 to 2012

For the client 7-11, was responsible for removing old equipment and installed a new NEC server, switch, router, UPS, monitor and network printer at each location. Programmed all handheld and flatbed scanners and tested all

new equipment for proper functionality

Representative achievement: Recommended and requested for several return engagements and visits with clients due to superior performance and continual success with solving problems

Kforce

September 2008 to 2012

Dependable performer working on numerous consulting assignments and regularly requested

by name from clients such as: Morgan Stanley, Liberty Mutual, and Lennox. Performing tasks that have included the deployment of Hewlett Packard and Dell PCs. Performing backup utilities for user's data, installing network and multi-function printer devices, and transfer existing data. Configuring users Outlook Express, Outlook 2003 accounts and performing onsite installation, training, and troubleshooting/support.

Representative achievement: Regularly praised by clients for ingenuity, dedication in resolving issues, a commitment to quality and success in meeting projected goals

Conexgen Tech

January 2007 to 2012

Performed data migration and software installation of all versions of Windows. Set up, repaired and troubleshoot various manufacturers of computers and printers. Developed strong virus removal and problem solving skills

Representative achievement: Regularly praised by owner for ingenuity and dedication to resolving problems

Education

Associates of Science, Computer Maintenance 1994

Los Angeles Trade Tech

Los Angeles